animekon.com 2018-04-08

# Animekon - Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you (namely your IP address) when you submit a comment or vote.

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When registering on our website, you may be asked to enter your e-mail address. You may, however, visit our website anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
\- To validate the owner of a user account, in case of a password reset request

 **Do we use cookies?**

No. However, third-party websites may use them when we display ads, embed video streams, or otherwise include external code.

Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the websites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may only release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information (such as total monthly visits) may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Eligibility**

You must be 13 years of age or older to register for or use this website and the various services we provide on or through this webite. If you are older than 13 but under 18 years of age, by using this website and its services you are telling us that you and your parent or guardian have reviewed and consent to the terms of this privacy policy.

 **Children Under the Age of 13**

As a matter of policy, visitors known to be under the age of 13 are prohibited from registering for or using this webite or its services. In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), we also do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from anyone under the age of 13.

 **Your consent**

By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our privacy policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This privacy policy was last updated on June 18, 2010.

 **Contacting us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.animekon.com/

Serban Stokker Cheregi  
Oradea, Bihor  
Romania

 **Privacy policy customer pledge**

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:

\- Federal Trade Commission Fair  
\- Privacy Alliance

Respectfully,  
Serban Stokker Cheregi  
Animekon
